let questions = [
  {
    Question: "What does “Pedra“ mean in English?",
    option: ["Lake", "Castle", "Stone", "Pensive"],
    correctAnswer: "Stone",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Filosofal“ mean in English?",
    option: ["Philosopher", "Parselmouth", "Patronus", "Firebolt"],
    correctAnswer: "Philosopher",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “Stone“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["Para", "Pelos", "Porta", "Pedra"],
    correctAnswer: "Pedra",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “Philosopher“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["Fechadura", "Filosofal", "Ficaria", "Pertencia"],
    correctAnswer: "Filosofal",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Capítulo“ mean in English?",
    option: ["Chapter", "Centaur", "Chaser", "Chamber"],
    correctAnswer: "Chapter",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “Chapter“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["Contrariar", "Compras", "Capítulo", "Calcanhares"],
    correctAnswer: "Capítulo",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Menino“ mean in English?",
    option: ["Magical", "Boy", "Men", "Bat"],
    correctAnswer: "Boy",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “Boy“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["Melhor", "Mundo", "Mais", "Menino"],
    correctAnswer: "Menino",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Sobreviveu“ mean in English?",
    option: ["Spilching", "Salamader", "Survived", "Seeker"],
    correctAnswer: "Survived",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “Survived“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["Subiram", "Sozinho", "Sentado", "Sobreviveu"],
    correctAnswer: "Sobreviveu",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Sr e Sra“ mean in English?",
    option: ["His and hers", "Survived", "To be or not to be", "Mr and Mrs"],
    correctAnswer: "Mr and Mrs",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “Mr and Mrs“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["Sir e Sar", "Sr e Sra", "En y Ena", "Nr e Nra"],
    correctAnswer: "Sr e Sra",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Da rua dos“ mean in English?",
    option: [
      "Here to there",
      "Two of them",
      "From the street",
      "From the house",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "From the street",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “From the street“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["Na esquina", "Da rua dos", "Da cidade", "Pela rua"],
    correctAnswer: "Da rua dos",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Alfeneiros“ mean in English?",
    option: ["Privet", "Pivet", "Alfie", "Privet"],
    correctAnswer: "Privet",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “Privet“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["Achavam", "Alfeneiros", "Aguentar", "Aparecessem"],
    correctAnswer: "Alfeneiros",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Se orgulhavam“ mean in English?",
    option: ["They were proud", "Come look", "Get organised", "The order"],
    correctAnswer: "They were proud",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “They were proud“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["Eles eram maus", "Ser feliz", "Se orgulhavam", "Orgulhoso de ti"],
    correctAnswer: "Se orgulhavam",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “De dizer“ mean in English?",
    option: ["The speaker", "The speach", "To say", "To do"],
    correctAnswer: "To say",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “To say“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["O discurso", "Pendência", "O orador", "De dizer"],
    correctAnswer: "De dizer",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Que eram perfeitamente normais“ mean in English?",
    option: [
      "They are the favourite",
      "They are not perfect at all",
      "Who want to be normal, not perfect",
      "That they were perfectly normal",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "That they were perfectly normal",
  },
  {
    Question:
      "How do you say “That they were perfectly normal“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: [
      "Eles são os favoritos",
      "Quem quer ser normal, não perfeito",
      "Que eram perfeitamente normais",
      "Eles não são nada perfeitos",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Que eram perfeitamente normais",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “Eram as últimas pessoas“ mean in English?",
    option: [
      "They were the first men",
      "The people were second",
      "They were the last people",
      "The people are first",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "They were the last people",
  },
  {
    Question:
      "How do you say “They were the last people“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: [
      "Eles foram os primeiros homens",
      "Eram as últimas pessoas",
      "O povo ficou em segundo lugar",
      "As pessoas estão em primeiro lugar",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Eram as últimas pessoas",
  },
  {
    Question: "What does “No mundo que se“ mean in English?",
    option: [
      "Whole wide world",
      "In the world that",
      "The other planet",
      "In the city",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "In the world that",
  },
  {
    Question: "How do you say “In the world that“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: ["No mundo que se", "O mundo todo", "Na cidade", "O outro planeta"],
    correctAnswer: "No mundo que se",
  },
  {
    Question:
      "What does “Esperaria que se metessem alguma cois estranha ou misteriosa“ mean in English?",
    option: [
      "I would expect something to happen",
      "I wouldn't expect something strange to happen",
      "I would expect something strange and mysterious to happen",
      "I would expect something wonderful to happen",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I would expect something strange and mysterious to happen",
  },
  {
    Question:
      "How do you say “I would expect something strange and mysterious to happen“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: [
      "Esperaria que se metessem alguma cois estranha ou misteriosa",
      "Eu esperaria que algo acontecesse",
      "Esperaria que algo estranho acontecesse",
      "Eesperaria que algo maravilhoso acontecesse",
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Esperaria que se metessem alguma cois estranha ou misteriosa",
  },
  {
    Question:
      "What does “Porque simplesmente nao compactuavam com esse tipo de bobagem“ mean in English?",
    option: [
      "Because they always go along with this kind of nonsense",
      "Because simply nonsense is bad",
      "Because simply they just didn't go along with this kind of nonsense",
      "Because simply it is all nonsense",
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Because simply they just didn't go along with this kind of nonsense",
  },
  {
    Question:
      "How do you say “Because simply they just didn't go along with this kind of nonsense“ in Brazillian Portuguese?",
    option: [
      "Porque eles sempre concordam com esse tipo de bobagem",
      "Porque simplesmente nao compactuavam com esse tipo de bobagem",
      "Porque simplesmente é tudo bobagem",
      "Porque simplesmente bobagem é ruim",
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Porque simplesmente nao compactuavam com esse tipo de bobagem",
  },
];
